serverbear.com 2013-04-30

# ServerBear Privacy Policy

## What information do we collect?

We only collect information from you when you run a server benchmark, this includes your email address & an optional field for the price you currently pay for your hosting package / server.

We also collect certain information about your server when you run our Benchmark, this includes: 

  * Operating System Name
  * Free RAM & Disk Space
  * UnixBench Benchmark Results
  * IO Speed
  * Data Transfer Speed

## What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

  * To provide a customised server benchmark report, we will use any information collected then compare it against other hosting plans to provide a report via email, the benchmark data is then anonymised & displayed on the ServerBear website to be used as comparison for other reports.
  * To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you).
  * To send periodic emails (The email address you provide for benchmarking, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your benchmark. If you opt in you may in also recieve occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

## How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information.

## Do we use cookies?

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits, keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

## Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

## Third party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

## California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

## Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

## Online Privacy Policy Only

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

## Terms and Conditions

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at <http://serverbear.com/terms>.

## Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to the ServerBear privacy policy.

## Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will update the Privacy Policy modification date below.

This policy was last modified on _**25th June 2012**_

## Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us via our [contact form](http://serverbear.com/contact).
